what's up everyone today five here with
a very special video today I was
watching the City Science and Christmas
special and [ __ ] and my mom walked in
and and I and I paused it so so I could
talk to her and I couldn't believe this
screenshot that that I pause on like
what the [ __ ] am I seeing like like just
ignoring how bad the animation is for a
second Sid Sid looks like he just took
like the fattest [ __ ] [ __ ] like out
of his ass and look at Jill look just
staring at his ass like you know you
know he's into that [ __ ] and like he's
doing like a fat
oh my God it's allos and [ __ ] because
you know it's like Christmas and [ __ ]
what the [ __ ] and he's running like a a
stupid like like dinosaur shirt because
you know he he wore that school to try
to turn to see the Science Kid on but
it's just not working because like Sid's
like straight and [ __ ] but oh my [ __ ]
god that clearly isn't stopping Sid the
Science Kid for taking the fat ass
[ __ ] dog like imaginable and and just
look at your face you can tell he's into
that [ __ ] like he wants to put his head
down there he would smell that [ __ ] I
don't give